Guide to the John A. Wilkinson, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1976-1984; Accession 1987-A-047
  - Administrative Files, 1976-1984
    - Board of Higher Education (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - CCIC (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - CCIC (Box 3, Folder 29 - 30)
    - Campus Police
      - 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 31 - 33)
      - 1983 (Box 5, Folder 34 - 35)
      - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 36 - 37)
      - 1981 (Box 5, Folder 38 - 39)
      - 1981 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - 1979 Aug - 1980 Dec 31 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Alarm Monitoring Project (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Benefits (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - Budget (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - JF [?] (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - Police Legislation (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Security reports (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Security surveys (Box 7, Folder 51 - 52)
      - Sergeant Search Comm. (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Community Relations
      - General Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 54 - 55)
      - General Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 56 - 57)
      - Athletic Tickets (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Bowl, Yale (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Day care (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Facilities, used (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Legislation (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - N. H. Symphony (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Police Legislation (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Revenue Com., 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Revenue Com., 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - Taxes (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - Upper Chapel Neighborhood Improvement Assoc. (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Corporation
      - General (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Accommodations (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - Alumni Fellow Nominating Committee (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - Candidates (Box 9, Folder 73 - 74)
      - Committees (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Fellows of the Corporation (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - Investor Responsibility (Box 10, Folder 77 - 79)
    - C -- General Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 80 - 83)
    - Campus Mail (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Cardiovascular Program (Box 11, Folder 85 - 87)
    - Carillon Committee -- Yale (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Chaplain Vannorsdall (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Child Study Center (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Commencement -- Baccalaureate (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Cornptroller's Office (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Conn. Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Council, Yale College (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - D -- General Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Deaths (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Development -- General (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Dining Halls (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Draft Registration/Student Aid (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Drama School (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Dwight Hall (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - E -- General Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Edwards, Jonathan College (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Eleven O'Clock Meeting (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Energy (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - F -- General Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 106 - 107)
    - Foreign Students and Scholars (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - Friday Group, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Friday Group, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - G -- General Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - General Counsel Office (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - German Visits (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Giamatti, A. Bartlett (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - Glee Club (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - H -- General Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 118 - 119)
    - Handicapped Committee (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - Harden Furniture (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - Holiday Dinners (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - Human Relations Counselors (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - I -- General Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - I.D. Cards (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - Information Office, Yale (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - Italian Art Restoration (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - J -- General Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - Judaic Studies (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - K -- General Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - Keys (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - Knights of Columbus (Box 15, Folder 134)
    - L -- General Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Law School (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - Lee, R.C. (Box 16, Folder 137)
    - Lustman Memorial (Box 16, Folder 138)
    - M -- General Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - Medal, Yale (Box 16, Folder 140)
    - Medical School (Box 16, Folder 141)
    - Minority Advisory Council (Box 16, Folder 142 - 143)
    - Minority Student Coordinators (Box 16, Folder 144)
    - Music School (Box 16, Folder 145)
    - N -- General Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 146)
    - N. H. Development Commission, 1980 July (Box 17, Folder 147)
    - Nuts and Sluts (Box 17, Folder 148)
    - O -- General Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 149)
    - Organization and Management, School of (Box 17, Folder 150)
    - P -- General Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 151)
    - Personnel Offrce (Box 17, Folder 152)
    - Pierson, George W. (Box 17, Folder 153)
    - Pierson College (Box 17, Folder 154)
    - Priorities and Planning Council (Box 18, Folder 155)
    - Pritzker Arch. Prize Comm. (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - Q -- General Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - R -- General Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 158)
    - Residential Colleges 50th (Box 18, Folder 160)
    - S -- General Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 161 - 162)
    - Science Park, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 163 - 164)
    - Science Park, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 165 - 166)
    - Search Committees (Box 19, Folder 167)
    - Secretaries Ivy (Box 20, Folder 168)
    - Seven Springs Center (Box 20, Folder 169 - 170)
    - Summer/Special Programs (Box 20, Folder 172)
    - T -- General Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 173)
    - Teacher Preparation Program (Box 21, Folder 175)
    - Terry Lectureship Committee (Box 21, Folder 176)
    - Trowbridge House (Box 21, Folder 178)
    - U -- General Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 179)
    - Union, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 181 - 182)
    - Union, 1977-1983 (Box 22, Folder 183 - 184)
    - United Way -- Yale Campaign (Box 22, Folder 185)
    - University Council -- General (Box 22, Folder 186)
    - University Directory (Box 22, Folder 187)
    - V -- General Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 187)
    - W -- General Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 188)
    - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar (Box 23, Folder 189)
    - X-Y-Z -- General Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 190)
    - Yale-China Association (Box 23, Folder 191)
    - Yale College Dean's Office (Box 24, Folder 192)
    - Yale Free Press (Box 24, Folder 193)
    - Yale Lit. Folder #2 (Box 24, Folder 194)
    - Yale Name -- Protection of (Box 24, Folder 195)
    - Telephone Message Forms, 1982 July 26-1983 December [13] (Box 25, Folder 196 - 200)
    - Mail Log, 1982 January-1984 July [31] (Box 26, Folder 201 - 204)
    - Bronze plaque: Games of the Olympiad, Seoul, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 205)
  - Secretary Wilkinson's Committees, 1979-1984
    - Albertus Magnus College (Box 27, Folder 206)
    - American Red Cross (Box 27, Folder 207)
    - Artspace, Inc. (Box 27, Folder 208)
    - BVA Steering Committee (Box 27, Folder 209)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 27, Folder 210)
    - Chamber Ad Hoc Econ. Develop Com. (Box 27, Folder 211)
    - Class of 1960 -- 25th Reunion (Box 27, Folder 212)
    - Class of 1960 (Box 27, Folder 213)
    - Convention and Visitors Bureau Bd. (Box 27, Folder 214)
    - Council for Urban Econ. Develop. (Conn-Coed) (Box 27, Folder 215)
    - Downtown Council
      - 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 216)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 217)
      - 1979-1982 Jul 31 (Box 27, Folder 218)
    - Elm Haven Committee Members (Box 27, Folder 219)
    - Hopkins School (Box 27, Folder 220)
    - New Haven Boys' Clubs (Box 27, Folder 221)
    - N. H. Devel. Admin. Search Com. (Box 27, Folder 222)
    - N. H. Develop. Com. Bio-Tech. Mkt. Com. (Box 27, Folder 223)
    - N. H. Development Corporation (Box 27, Folder 224)
    - Portsmouth School (Box 28, Folder 225)
    - St. Martin De Torres (Box 28, Folder 226)
    - St. Thomas More (Box 28, Folder 227)
    - United Way Search Com. (Box 28, Folder 228)
    - Y-NHH Board Members lists (Box 28, Folder 229)
    - Y-NHH, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 230)
  - Security Committee Files, 1980-1984
    - Catherine Skinner's Committee Files (as Chairman), 1977-1982 (Box 29, Folder 231 - 244)
    - Security Committee
      - 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 245 - 246)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 247 - 248)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 249 - 250)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 251 - 252)
    - Security -- Rape Seminars (Box 32, Folder 253)
    - Security Budget (Box 32, Folder 254)
    - Security Com. Minutes and Agendum, 1980-1984 July 31 (Box 32, Folder 255)
    - Security Com. Minutes/Agendum, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 256)
    - Banner Office, Yale (Box 33, Folder 257)
    - Berkeley College (Box 33, Folder 258)
    - Bingham Hall (Box 33, Folder 259)
    - Branford College (Box 33, Folder 260)
    - Calhoun College (Box 33, Folder 261)
    - Cross Campus (Box 33, Folder 262)
    - Crown Street #301, #305, #295-297 (Box 33, Folder 263)
    - Davenport College (Box 33, Folder 264)
    - Dwight College, Timothy (Box 33, Folder 265)
    - Edwards College, Jonathan (Box 33, Folder 266)
    - G and P Student Senate (Box 33, Folder 267)
    - Harkness Hall, W.L. (Box 33, Folder 268)
    - Hendrie Hall (Box 33, Folder 269)
    - KBT and JWG (Box 33, Folder 270)
    - Kirtland Hall (Box 33, Folder 271)
    - Law School (Box 33, Folder 272)
    - Mansfield Apartments (Box 33, Folder 273)
    - Mansfield St, #173-175 (Box 33, Folder 274)
    - Mini-Bus (Box 33, Folder 275)
    - Morse College (Box 33, Folder 276)
    - Park Street #205 (Box 33, Folder 277)
    - Park Street #217 (Cabaret) (Box 33, Folder 278)
    - Parking Lot #34 (Box 33, Folder 279)
    - Pierson College (Box 33, Folder 280)
    - Silliman College (Box 33, Folder 281)
    - Ezra Stiles (Box 33, Folder 282)
    - Street Hall and Old Art Gallery (Box 33, Folder 283)
    - SSS (Box 33, Folder 284)
    - Trumbull College (Box 33, Folder 285)
    - Wall Street -- 53 (Box 33, Folder 286)
    - Woolsey Hall (Box 33, Folder 287)
    - York Street (Box 33, Folder 288)
    - York Street #222 -- Yale Theatre (Box 33, Folder 289)
- Printed reports, 1931-1976; Accession 1987-A-079
  Open for research.
  - Constitutions, By-laws and Agreements of Organizations Associated with Yale University (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Inaugural Address by A. Whitney Griswold, 1950 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Proposal for the Creation of an Institute for Social Science, 1968 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Institution for Social Policy Studies; General Statement, 1973 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Visiting Fellowships in Timothy Dwight College--The Chubb, The Arts and Letters (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Remarks of President John F. Kennedy, 1962 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Class of 1960, Its Origins, Performance, and Plans -- Office of Educational Research -- Pauls Burnham, Director, 1960 December 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dwyer Report -- Alumni Affairs, Report of the Commission on, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Services, Governance Report, University, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Teaching and Learning, Report of the Commission on -- Faculty Chairman, Michael McBride, 1975 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fellowships, Yale Residential College -- Report of an Ad Hoc Committee, 1971 April (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Yale College, Report of the Study Group on, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dwight Hall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Retirement Allowances, Provisions for -- Supplement to the Yale Corporation, 1969 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Report of the President's Committee on General Education, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Approaches to Yale University (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memorandum to Students of Yale University Re: The Confrontation Problem, 1969 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Athletics, Report of the Yale University Commission on -- Gerard Jones, Chairman, 1976 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Report to the President of Yale University on the Role of the Arts in Undergraduate Education at Yale, 1967 January (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Summary of Operative Privisions of the Yale Charter and Legislation (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Report of the President's Ad Hoc Committee on the ROTC to the Faculty of Yale College (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - A Comic History of Yale -- Fairfax Downey, '16 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Windows of Dwight Memorial Chapel (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The University Library, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Noah Webster and the Dawn of Linguistic Science, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - A Talk by Reuben A. Holden -- Vermont and Yale, 1965 July 27 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dedication of the Yale Computer Center, 1962 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Baccalaureate Address by A. Whitney Griswold, 1958 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The University, and Interview with A. Whitney Griswold, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Funeral Service -- A. Whitney Griswold, 1963 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Medicine and Science at Yale (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Report of the President's Advisory Committee -- Henry Sloane Coffin, '97, Chairman, 1952 February 9 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Noah Webster (Commemoration Events), 1958 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The Choice of an Occupation -- Crawford and Harrower, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Cinstitution and By-Laws of the Alumni Board of Yale University, 1952 June 14 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Dunham Laboratory -- Yale University, 1958 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Description of the Sterling Law Buildings at Yale University, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Yale Summer Intern Program in Government -- A Reports on the 1958 Experimental Program, 1958 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Reverend Anson Phelps Stokes -- Yale's Christian Tradition (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Opportunities for Postgraduate Study and Employment and Summer Programs, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Eating at Yale 1701-1965 -- Loomis Havemeyer, 1965 December (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Yale's Extracurricular and Social organizations, 1780-1960 -- Loornis Havemeyer, 1961 January (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The Report of the President's Committee on the Freshman Year -- Leonard W. Doob, Chairman, 1962 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Lohman, Carl A. -- When We Bade Young Yale Farewell, 1937 December (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Yale-in-China Association -- YALI, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Dwight Hall -- Seventy-Fifth Anniversary, 1956 November 4 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Harvard Lecture -- The Stability of Dictatorships -- Alexander Gerrschenkron, 1963 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Handbook for Association Officers -- Yale Alumni Board (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Woodward Lecture, Congress and Parliament -- The Honorable Howard Beale, Q. C., 1960 November 28 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Service of Remembrance -- Battell Chapel (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 1958 Jun 15 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 1960 Jun 18 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Peabody Museum -- Oceanographic and Orinthological Laboratories, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Mills, The Ad Hoc Committee for the Reinstatement of Kenneth, 1972 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Priorities and Planning, Council on, 1973 January 2 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - The Mechanics of a Novel -- John Hersey -- Vol. 27, No. 1, 1952 July (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Benjamin Silliman, Jr. -- Educator (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Shakespeare Festival, The Yale, 1954 February and March (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Graduate Placement, Committee, Yale -- Policies and Procedures, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Morse -- Dedication of College, 1962 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Stiles, Ezra -- Dedication of College, 1962 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Engineering Education at Yale, Report of the Committee for the Study of, 1961 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Counseling and Placement -- A Guide to Employment Study -- Summer Opportunities, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Selective Service, Office of Military Service -- Opportunities and Obligations, 1962 April (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Alumni Association -- Alumni Day, 1960 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Bozyan, H. Frank -- Memorial Organ, 1971 November 3 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Transportation at Yale University, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Divinity School -- Bainton, Roland H. -- Men Memorialized in the Buildings, 3 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Yale Today -- Undergraduate Admissions Office, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - The Silliman House -- Carl Purington Rollins Press, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Nathanial Chauncey -- Class of 1702 -- Herbert Thomas (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Undergraduate Regulations, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Alumni House (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Brewster, President Kingman -- The Mystery of Our Success -- Alumni Day, 1966 February 19 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Undergraduate Calendar, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Printer's Solutions of Some Printers' Problems, 1955 January 7 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Brewster, Kingman -- An Address Given at the Dedication of the Student Center, New Haven College, 1965 November 1 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Libraries, Yale, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Science and Engineering at Yale, A Short History of, 1955 October 28-29 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - The Yale-New Haven Medical Center -- An Address Given to the American Institute of Banking -- Vernon W. Lippard, M.D., Dean, 1961 February 25 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1970 July 1 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - The Mellon Fellows, 1932-1967 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Selective Service -- The Draft Law -- A "College Outline" for the Selective Service Act and Regulations (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Medical School -- Sesquicentennial Anniversary, 1810-1960 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Holden, Rueben A. -- China and Yale -- Reprinted from Venture -- Vol. V, No. 1, 1965 January (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Alumni Association -- Yale Goes to the Northwest -- Minneapolis-St. Paul Regional Meeting, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - War Memorial Dedication of the Memorial Tablets to the Yale Men who Lost their Lives in Korea 1950- 1953, 1959 February 21 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Collections Convocation, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Alumni Association -- Yale Alumni Day and Dedication of the Electron Accelerator Laboratory, 1962 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - David S. Ingalls Rink -- Dedication Game -- Yale vs. Dartmouth, 1959 February 21 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - University Council -- 1948-1963, 1968 October (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Franklin, Benjamin, Acceptance of (Book) on Behalf of Yale; W. S. Lewis, 3 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Batteries, Yale -- Fairfax Downey, B.B. 1916 -- Privately Printed, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Brewster, Kingman -- Style, Pluck, and Integrity, 1969 December (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Residential Colleges -- Yale's Stake in the Residential Priciple: Evidence from the British Experience -- Griswold and Mendenhall, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney -- For the Arts and Sciences at Yale -- A Special Report of the President of the University, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Women at Yale, Committee on the Status of Professional -- Report to the President -- Thomas M. Greene, Chairman, 197[?] (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard -- Professor's Theory and Its Practical Uses, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney -- Griswold's Building Years at Yale -- Reprinted from Architectural Forum, 1963 June (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - The Connecticut Mental Health Center -- The Dedication Ceremonies, 1966 September 30 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health at Yale -- Dedication of the Laboratory, 1965 April 10 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Acceleration, Report of a Joint Subcornmiteee of the Executive Committee and the Courses of Study Committee on; Chairman -- Martin Griffin, 1975 February (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - The Kline Biology Tower at Yale -- Dedication -- Account with Speeches, 1966 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Art and Architecture School -- Dedication, 1963 November 9 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Fisher, Irving, Centennial of the Birth of -- 1867-1967, 1967 March 2 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Printers at Yale University; Random Notes on the Origin of the College Presses together with a History of the Honorable Company -- George D. Vaill, 1967 May (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Printers -- From Manuscript. to Offset Printing -- Carl P. Rollins 1919-1948, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - The Residential Colleges at Yale University, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Parents' Day -- agenda, 1967 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Theodore Sizer 1892-1967 -- Funeral Service, 1967 September 30 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - University Council, Dinner in Honor of the Tenth Anniversary of the, 1958 February 21 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Yale College -- 250th Anniversary, 1968 July 6 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Undergraduate Prizes, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - The Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library at Yale University, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Deanships, Report of the Residential College -- Charles A. Walker, Chairman, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - The Yale Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Some Facts About Yale (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Yale University Capital Development Plan: Annual Report, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 125)
- Records concerning visitors, inaugurations, and security, 1977-1981; Accession 1987-A-102
  - Foreign Visitors
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Foreign Visitors statistics (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Short-term foreign visitors (ground rules) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Visitors program worksheets (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Visitors, information for (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Inaugurations
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10 - 12)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13 - 14)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15 - 16)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 17 - 18)
    - Previous (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Security Committee
    - Agenda (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Art and Architecture (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Brochure (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Student patrol (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Budget (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - University Security Committee Budget
    - Charges (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Estimates (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Minutes/Agenda (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Projects Completed (Box 5, Folder 33 - 34)
    - Projects Pending (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Surveys (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Security - Campus (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Security Complaints (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Security Committee
    - Crime Prevention (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Divinity School (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - General (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Security
    - Lighting (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Locks/Keys (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Masters' Houses (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Security - Master Keys (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - University Security Committee - Medical School (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Security Committee
    - Membership (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Minutes (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Security - Off Campus (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Security Committee
    - Parking (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Pending (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Police Priorities (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Security - Poster Program (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Security Committee
    - Publicity (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - 1976 Report (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Security Week (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Seminars (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - University Security Committee - Statement of Purpose (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Security
    - Statistics (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Telephones (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Transportation (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Phone logs, appointment books, and confidential records, 1932-1987; Accession 1988-A-008
  - Telephone Message Books
    - 1983 Dec 23 - 1984 Oct 29 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 7)
    - 1984 Oct 29 - 1985 Oct 14 (Box 2, Folder 8 - 13)
    - 1985 Oct 14 - 1986 Oct 9 (Box 3, Folder 14 - 20)
  - Corporation Residences Committee